{
    "id": "381cdd5ed4cb4f1089e4670dadd717d2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You don’t know what has happened, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e2c0841d8784fedbadffb585f0d65f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "While passing ………………… the small door, I hurt my head.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f6fc64abbe4402a8644b3cc09be2a85"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief was caught …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "green-handed",
                "blue-handed",
                "red-handed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a58704c4bc954985b07aa3a83b456b9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If something is ‘All Greek and Latin to you’, you ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "understand it",
                "don't understand it",
                "find it amusing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bea1f322b69d4617b3ee85eaea258365"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to ask …………………… more questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8317c54aaba84daa901f713740355d6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The player announced that he ……………………… from the game.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is retiring",
                "was retiring",
                "will retire"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da49a2f8867743589711966d0752adb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though they were badly outnumbered, the soldiers decided to make a ………………….. effort to conquer the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last hole",
                "last ditch",
                "last cannon"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8739aa406a984c5c8e51d81f988f1884"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students ……………………… when the teacher walked into the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand up",
                "stood up",
                "have stood up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f63299f42794f13bc8e1c9c7c4acdfa"
        },
        {
            "question": "They won’t accept this proposal, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will they",
                "won't they",
                "would they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7911eb376934f9b81ad8fed8201f2b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait …………………… I return?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "when",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eb4eff5ca1394317a42f8f625dddc6fe"
        }
    ]
}